<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on Tealford Consulting</title><link>/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on Tealford Consulting</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 10:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Is Still Worth Learning How To Code In 2025?</title><link>/projects/learn-to-code-is-this-still-true-in-2025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 10:01:35 +0300</pubDate><guid>/projects/learn-to-code-is-this-still-true-in-2025/</guid><description>Coding has been one of the most talked-about skills of the last decade. From tech giants to small startups, programming has been championed as the golden ticket to career growth, innovation, and financial stability. But with new tools like AI automating parts of programming and non-technical roles gaining importance, many are asking: is it still worth learning to code in 2025? This article explores the question through five key lenses: relevance, accessibility, industry demand, alternatives, and the future outlook.</description></item><item><title>What Is The Metaverse? And Is It Inevitable</title><link>/projects/what-is-the-metaverse-and-is-it-inevitable/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 10:01:35 +0300</pubDate><guid>/projects/what-is-the-metaverse-and-is-it-inevitable/</guid><description>The metaverse has captured imaginations worldwide, presenting a vision where digital and physical realities merge into one continuous experience. For some, it represents the next stage of the internet—a place where we do more than browse content; we step into it. For others, it feels like an overhyped buzzword that still lacks practical grounding. Either way, the concept is here, and powerful forces are driving it forward.
This article explores five key questions about the metaverse.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Website Shouldn’t Be Built on a Template (And What to Do Instead)</title><link>/projects/why-your-website-shouldnt-be-built-on-a-template/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:01:35 +0300</pubDate><guid>/projects/why-your-website-shouldnt-be-built-on-a-template/</guid><description>When you’re launching a business or refreshing your brand, it’s tempting to build your website on a platform like Squarespace, Wix, or WordPress. After all, they promise quick setup, beautiful designs, and low monthly costs. But while these services look appealing at first glance, they often create long-term problems—especially for businesses that plan to grow.
At Tealford Consulting, we work with many clients who started with these platforms and later felt stuck, limited, or invisible online.</description></item><item><title>Is AI the New Intern? How Small Businesses Can Use AI Without Losing Their</title><link>/projects/is-ai-the-new-intern/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 08:01:35 +0300</pubDate><guid>/projects/is-ai-the-new-intern/</guid><description>It seems like everywhere you turn these days, someone’s talking about artificial intelligence (AI). From writing blog posts to answering emails, AI is quickly becoming a tool that many businesses are turning to for help. But if you&amp;rsquo;re running a small business, you might wonder: is this just hype? Will AI take over? Or can it actually help without changing who you are?
The truth is, AI can be a powerful assistant—as long as you stay in control.</description></item><item><title>Your Digital Footprint Is a Business Asset</title><link>/projects/your-digital-footprint-is-a-business-asset/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:01:35 +0300</pubDate><guid>/projects/your-digital-footprint-is-a-business-asset/</guid><description>Most small business owners think about their logo, storefront, or business cards when they hear the word “brand.” But in today’s world, your digital footprint—the trail your business leaves online—is just as important, if not more. It&amp;rsquo;s how people find you, research you, trust you, and ultimately decide whether or not to work with you.
At Tealford Consulting, we think of your digital footprint as one of your most valuable business assets.</description></item><item><title>Web3 for Small Business - Hype or Opportunity?</title><link>/projects/web3-hype-or-opportunity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:01:35 +0300</pubDate><guid>/projects/web3-hype-or-opportunity/</guid><description>You’ve probably heard the term Web3 thrown around in tech circles, social media, or even casual conversations—often surrounded by buzzwords like blockchain, NFTs, or decentralization. For small business owners, it can all feel a little abstract or even irrelevant. After all, what does this next version of the internet have to do with running a restaurant, a boutique, or a local service business?
At Tealford Consulting, we believe that while Web3 is still developing, it’s not just hype—it’s a shift in how the internet works.</description></item></channel></rss>